

I am a UI/UX designer with 7+ years of design experience, specializing in building scalable front-end products with great user experiences. I am currently looking for a hybrid UX designer and developer position to support between design and development.

PORTFOLIO

Website jaykim-dev.netlify.app

CONTACT

Phone +1 (469) 386-6307

Email develop.jay8675@gmail.com

Address Dallas, Texas

SOCIAL

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/jay8675

Github github.com/jaehyung8675

SKILLS

Design User Experience (UX)

User Interface (UI)

Product Graphic Visual

Programming JavaScript

React Node.js Express.js HTML5 CSS

Sass / SCSS

Tools Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Figma Git Github

Visual Studio Code

EXPERIENCE

Sr. UI/UX Designer

January 2020 – January 2023 Carrollton, Texas

OTA World LLC

- Led a design team to create and improve all product designs, and maintained corporate websites.
- Responsible for maintaining content and style attributes of marketing and e-commerce sites.
- Managed content management applications with creative marketing tools.
- Designed and developed products, and used by over 100+ merchants to market their sites.
- Managed projects using Agile to quickly deliver products to stakeholders, vendors, and customers.

Visual Designer / Part-time

July 2017 - Present

Binnerri Presbyterian Church

Richardson, Texas

Dallas, Texas

- Created all visual designs for over 400+ members to engage them in worship and events.
- Redesigned 2+ websites to make them more visually and experientially accessible to customers.
- Created presentations for speakers to support their sermons and easily interact with the audience.
- Completed projects on time and delivered to clients according to the church's schedule and goals.

Graphic Designer

January 2014 – December 2014

Ravis's Ware House

- Created designs that help market and promote products and features.
- Worked within existing visual guidelines to create compelling, and brand-centric design solutions.
- Owned design projects and brought them to completion, working with stakeholders to update.

Product Designer / Internship

January 2010 – January 2011 Seoul, South Korea

Pantech Wireless, Inc.

- Completed 2 major projects with all mobile design processes from concept to building prototypes.
- Explored interaction design through research, persona, user journey map, storyboard, and user flow.
- Worked with team members to implement new product ideas using design thinking.

EDUCATION

University of North Texas2020 – 2022M.A. in Interaction DesignDenton, Texas

Southern Methodist University2017 – 2019B.F.A. in Art & Graphic DesignDallas, Texas

Brookhaven College2014 – 2017

A.A. in General Studies

Farmers Branch, Texas

Christian For The Nations Institute2012 – 2013Accredited Theological DegreeDallas, Texas

Hongik University2006 – 2010

B.A. in Product Design

Sejong, South Korea